how's it going everyone
cameras off in fact with a very special
video today and I've got some pretty
terrible nose as you can see from the
title
it hurts me really bad to say this but
this year that is not going to be a
Halloween special
I know Halloween is smile I waited too
long to upload this but I just gotta say
it here and now this is going down today
I did not make a homey video and there's
a very good explanation for that but I'm
sorry to make a big stinky poopy on your
dreams but this is just how it is I had
Halloween and Thanksgivings dates mixed
up I thought Halloween was in November
and Thanksgiving was on October 31st and
I didn't find out until very recently
that it's the other way around
I I'm not gonna apologize because I have
nothing to bother about I can do
whatever the [ __ ] I want [ __ ] although
yeah that's basically how it is now I do
have a Thanksgiving video in the works
at the moment actually it's finished yes
it is finished although I mean it really
sucks balls because I know how much
people like my Halloween specials every
[ __ ] year so to come out and say this
uh uh I don't apologize and [ __ ] but
that's how it is [ __ ]